Guide to the Matthew F. McHugh papers, 1974-1992.
McHugh, Matthew F papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Matthew F. McHugh papers, 1974-1992.
4536
McHugh, Matthew F.(Matthew Francis),
192 cubic ft.
Correspondence, printed materials, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
General files, correspondence, notebooks, press clippings, and cassette tapes.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Matthew F. McHugh was a Democratic member of the United States House of Representatives from New York State. McHugh was born in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania in 1938 and attended Mount St. Mary's University and Villnova University School of Law. He was the district attorney of Tompkins County, New York from 1969 to 1972. McHugh was elected to Congress in 1974 and served from 1975 until 1993, participating as a member of the Appropriations, Intelligence, and Ethics Committees, as well as the Committees on Agriculture, Interior, Veterans Affairs, and Children, Youth and Families. After retiring from Congress, he was the vice president of Cornell University and later worked for the World Bank.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
General files, correspondence, notebooks, press clippings, and cassette tapes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
McHugh, Matthew F. 1938-; United States. Congress. House -- Officials and employees.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Collection restricted to permission of the donor.
CONTAINER LIST
- 094th Congress 01, 1975 - 1976 (Box 209)
  Bills H.J. 00285 - H.R. 04154.
- 094th Congress 02, 1975 - 1976 (Box 203)
  Bills H.R. 04190 - H.R. 10265.
- 094th Congress 03, 1975 - 1976 (Box 207)
  Bills H.R. 10355 - H.R. 13166.
- 094th Congress 04, 1975 - 1976 (Box 212)
  Bills H.R. 13275 - H.R. 15638.
- 094th Congress 05, 1975 - 1976 (Box 249)
  Large binders, Bills Introduced by McHugh (bk 2), Feb 1979 Civil Aeronautics Board Orders, re Sullivan County/Allegheny Airlines, "Deleted Computer Texts", McHugh Co-Sponsored Legislation (2 binders), McHugh Co-Signed Statements (2 binders).
- 095th Congress, 1977 - 1978 (Box 184)
  Hundreds of small files.
- 095th Congress, 1977 - 1978 (Box 217)
  Bills H.R. 10611 - 14378, 38 others unnumbered, Large folder of cosigned statements.
- 095th Congress, 1977 - 1978 (Box 230)
  Bills (official printed versions).
- 095th Congress 1st Session, 1977 - 1978 (Box 182)
  Resolutions.
- 095th Congress 1st Session, 1977 - 1978 (Box 191)
- 096th Congress, 1979 - 1980 (Box 231)
  Four large binders, FY79 Appropriations Bill Floor Book, FY80 Appropriations Bill Foreign Assistance & Related Programs (HR 4473) Floor Book, D of Treasury Report on International Financial Institutions, "Case for a Global Marshall Plan" (Carter Policy).
- 096th Congress, 1979 - 1981 (Box 145)
  Bills.
- 096th Congress-097th Congress, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 34)
  Legislation Cosponsor Invitations (1979), Local District Budget Hearing Files (1981, 1982, 1983).
- 097th Congress, 1981 - 1983 (Box 146)
- 097th Congress, 1981 - 1983 (Box 150)
  Bills, Co-Signed Statements.
- 098th Congress, 1983 - 1985 (Box 31)
  Legislation Cosponsor Invitations.
- 098th Congress, 1983 - 1985 (Box 145)
  Bills, See also Box 146, Co-Signed Statements.
- 098th Congress, 1983 - 1985 (Box 146)
  Bills, See also Box 145, Co-Signed Statements 1983-1984.
- 099th Congress, 1985 - 1986 (Box 251)
  McHugh Co-Sponsored Legislation, McHugh Co-Signed Statements.
- 099th Congress, 1985 - 1987 (Box 70)
- 100th Congress, 1987 - 1988 (Box 250)
- 100th Congress, 1987 - 1988 (Box 252)
- 101st Congress, 1989 - 1991 (Box 2)
  Cosigned Statements, Sponsored/Co-Sponsored Legislation.
- 101st Congress, 1989 - 1991 (Box 147)
- 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box 253)
  McHugh Retirement Letters (two large files).
- 102nd Congress, 1991 - 1992 (Box 288)
  McHugh Sponsored and Co-Sponsored Legislation, McHugh Co-Signed Statements, Legislative Profile 1991-1992.
- 102nd Congress Activity Guide, 1992 (Box 193)
  In five unlabelled folders 264 pps and Appendix A.
- Airline Deregulation 1979 - 1983, 1979 - 1983 (Box 239)
  Half the box is Airline Deregulation files.
- Appropriations Committee 095, 1977 - 1978 (Box 210)
  Appropriations - Legislative Sub-Committee, Appropriations - Agriculture, Rural Development & Related Agencies, Appropriations - Defense Sub-Committee, Appropriations - District of Columbia Sub-Committee, Appropriations - Labor Health Education & Welfare, Appropriations - Military Construction Sub-Committee (empty), Appropriations - Public Works Sub-Committee, Appropriations - State, Justice, Commerce, Judiciary Sub-Committee, Appropriations - Transportation Sub-Committee, Appropriations - Treasury Postal Service General Government Sub-Committee, Appropriations, Appropriations - Foreign Operations Sub-Committee, Appropriations - HUD Independent Agencies, Appropriations - Interior - Pine Voles, Appropriations - Interior Sub-Committee, USAID Congressional Presentation FY 1979, Annex A, Annex B.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 095-01, 1977 - 1978 (Box 151)
  Arms Sales Notifications, Committee Rules & Related Materials, Committee FY 1978 Recissions, Foreign Operations Subcommittee, FY 1978 Supplementals, Africa, AID ASHA, AID Contingency Fund, AID Disaster Assistance, AID Education & Human Resources, AID Food & Nutrition, AID General, AID Health, AID FY 1978 India Reprogramming, AID Operating Expenses, AID Population Planning, AID Program Changes - Africa, AID Program Changes - Asia, AID Program Changes - Latin America, AID Program Changes - Middle East, AID Program Changes - Other, AID Sahel Delopment Program, AID Technical Assistance, African Development Bank/Fund, Asian Development Bank/Fund, Cyprus, East Asia/Pacific Region - General, Export/Import Bank, General Statements on FY 1979 Requests, Human Rights.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 095-02, 1977 - 1978 (Box 234)
  InterAmerican Foundation, International Bank for Reconstruction & Development (2 files), International Development Association, InterAmerican Development Bank Fund for Special Operations, InterAmerican Development Bank Fund, International Financial Corporation, International Monetary Fund, International Financial Institutions, International Organizations, Israel/US Binational Agricultural Fund, Members of Congress for Peace Through Law, Middle East Arms Sales, Migration & Refugee Assistance, Military Assistance, Overseas Private Investment Corporation, Palm Oil, Panama, Peru.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 095-03, 1977 - 1978 (Box 237)
  Peace Corps, Public Witnesses (2 files), PL 480, Recissions for FY 1978, Saudi Arabia, Secretary of State, Security Supporting Assistance, South/Central Amercia, Steel, Trade Issues, Turkey, UN Disarmament, Vietnam, World Food Issus, Zimbabwe/Rhodesia, USAID 1978, Research Literature for Development Food/Nutrition v1 & v2, International Monetary Fund Annual Report 1978, “Some Possible Future Issues” - monograph, Cornell Rural Development Committee, Cornell Participation, Local Organization for Rural Development (Asia), 1978 World Bank World Development Report, 1978 World Bank Annual Report, 1979 Appropriations Bill Foreign Assistance & Related Programs, Title XII Handbook.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 095-04, circa 1980 (Box 77)
  Treaties & Executive Agreements, Tunisia, Turkey, Turkish Arms Embargo, Uganda, UN CTAD V, UN Development Program, UNICEF, Uruguay, Vietnam, Water Projects, World Food Issues, World Hunger Commission, Yemen (North), Yemen (South), Yugoslavia, Zaire, Zambia, Zimbabwe/Rhodesia, USAID Congressional Presentation FY 1980, (six bound volumes).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 095-05, 1979 (Box 233)
  Binders.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 096-01, 1979 - 1980 (Box 72)
  Asian Development Bank Fund, Appropriate Technology, Australia, Budget & Economic Outlook (General), Budget Resolutions, Recissions, Committee Rules & Related Materials, Supplementals, Africa, African Development Fund, AID FILES, ASHA, Contingency Fund, Cornell, Disaster Assistance, Education & Human Resources, Food & Nutrition, General, Health, Operating Expenses, Population, Sahel Development Program, Technical Assistance, Title XII, AIPAC, Algeria, Angola, Argentina, Arms Controls, Arms Spending in Developing Countries, Asia Foundation, Bangladesh, Bolivia, Brazil, Burma.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 096-02, 1979 - 1980 (Box 75)
  Cambodia, Cameroon, Camp David Accords, Central African Empire, Chad, Chile, China (Mainland), China (Taiwan), Columbia, Commodities, Comoros, Cornell Briefing, Costa Rica, Cuba, CUSLAR, Cyprus, Dominican Republic, East Asia/Racific Region, Economic Support Fund, Ecuador, Egypt, El Salvador, Equatorial Guinea, Ethiopia, Export-Import Bank.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 096-03, 1979 - 1980 (Box 65)
  El Salvador (3 files), Export-Import Bank (2 files), Ethiopia, Germany, Grenada, Greece, Guatemala (5 large files), Haiti, Hmong, Honduras, Human Rights (General), Human Rights (cases, 3 files), Indonesia, India, Infant Formula (1 of 3).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 096-04, 1980 - 1984 (Box 91)
  Infant Formula (2 and 3 of 3), Inter-American Development Bank, Inter-American Foundation, International Development Association, International Development Cooperative Agency, International Bank for Construction & Redevelopment, International Finance Corporation, Internaitonal Financial Institutions., International Fund for Agricultural Development (2 files), International Military Education & Training Program, International Monetary Fund, Fact sheet on Gramm Amendment (IMF Authorization), International Narcotics Control Program, International Organizations (general), Iran, Ireland, Ireland (Northern), Israel (5 files), Ivory Coast, Jamaica, Japan, Jordan, Kenya.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 096-05, 1980 - 1984 (Box 89)
  Korea, Laos, Law of the Seas Treaty, Lebanon, Lesotho, Liberia, Libya, Malaysia, Military Assistance Program (MAP) (2 files), Mauritania, Members of Congress for Peace Through Law, Middle East Bases, Migration & Refugees (4 files), Mondale File, Morroco, Mozambique, MX Missile, Namibia, Nicaragua (6 files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 096-06, 1981 - 1983 (Box 118)
  Nigeria, Nuclear Non-Proliferation, Oman, OPIC, Pakistan, Panama, Participatory Development, Peace Corps, Philippines, POW/MIA, P. L. 480, Romania, Singapore, Somalia, South Africa, DOS - Anti-Terrorism Assistance, DOS - Current Policy Papers (3 files), DOS - International Narcotics Control Program, DOS - Refugees, DOS - Peacekeeping Operations, Strategic Defense Initiative, Strategic Defense Initiative - Institute, Sudan, Tunisia.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 097-01, 1979 - 1982 (Box 108)
  Afghanistan, Africa Development Foundation, Africa Development Fund, AID Africa, AID ASHA, AID Asia, AID Education and Human Resources, AID Disaster Assistance, AID Deobligation/Reobligation, AID Food & Nutrition, AID General, AID Health, AID Latin America, AID Mixed Credits, AID Near East, AID Operating Expenses, AID Population, AID Private Enterprises, AID Sahel Development Program, AID Technical Assistance, AID Title XII, AID World Development Letter, AIPAC, Algeria, Ambassadors, Angola, Anti-Terrorism Assistance, Appropriations Committee Rules and Related Materials, Appropriations Committee Security Clearance, Argentina, Arms Control, Arms Spending in Developing Countries, ASATS (2 files), ASEAN, Asian Development Bank/Fund, Bangladesh, Belize, Bolivia, Brazil, Burma, Callable Capital, Cambodia, Cameroon, Caribbean Initiative (2 files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 097-02, 1981 - 1983 (Box 132)
  Central America - General, Central America - Trip File (3 files), Chad, Chile, China (Mainland), China (Taiwan), Congressional Forum on US and Developing Countries, Costa Rica, Cuba, CUSLAR, Cyprus (large), Debt Problem (International), Debt Relief, Democratic Caucus, Democratic Study Group, Democratic Study Group Task Force on Foreign Policy, Democratic Study Group Task Force on Taxes and Compensation, Dominican Republic, East Timor (3 large files), Economic Support Fund, Egypt, El Salvador (10 files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 097-03, 1981 - 1983 (Box 95)
  El Salvador Files 11-30.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 097-04, 1979 - 1980 (Box 102)
  Iran Hostage Crisis 1980 - Action File (small), Iran Hostage Crisis 1980 – Correspondence File (large), Peace Corps Country Management Plan FY 1980, Narcotics Control in Mexico (bound, 4 volumes) 1979, Institute for Technological Cooperation Congressional Presentation 1979, OAS Report on the Situation of Human Rights in Panama 1979, OAS Report on the Situation of Human Rights in Nicaragua 1978, Office of Refugee and Migration Affairs Congressional Presentation 1979, ASHA Lanaido Hospital File, McHugh Amendments to bills, Talking Points - India, Talking Points - Nicaragua.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 097-05, 1979 - 1981 (Box 71)
  International Narcotics control, Institute for Technological Coöperation, IFIs (General), IMF, International Organizations, Involving the Poor, Iran, Iraq, Ireland, Israel, Jamaica, Japan, Jordan, Kenya, Korea (Republic of), Korea (Peoples Republic of), Korean Influence Investigation, Laos, Latin America, Law of the Sea, Lebanon, Liberia, Libya.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-01, 1986 (Box 56)
  ABM Treaty, Afghanistan, African Development Bank Fund, African Development Foundation, African Food Crisis, Agency for International Development (AID) Files:, Africa, Agriculture, Rural Development, & Nutrition, Mixed Credits, Operating Expenses, Population (2 files), Private Enterprise, PVD Policy, Sahel Development Program, Title XII, Asia, Child Survival Fund, Economic Support, Education & Human Services, Disaster Assistance, General, Health, ASHA, AIPAC, Algeria, Angola, Appropriations Committee.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-02, 1987 - 1989 (Box 124)
  Arms Control & Foreign Political Caucus, Arms Control - General, Anti-Satellite Weapons (ASATs), Base Rights Agreements, Belize, Biological Weapons, Bolivia, Cambodia, Central America - General, Chile, China - Mainland, China - Taiwan, Contadora Peace Process, Costa Rica, Cuba, Cyprus, Dominican Republic, Ecuador, Egypt, El Salvador (3 large files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-03, 1987, 1988 (Box 59)
  Covert Action Briefing File, Foreign Aid Appropriations (FY1986), Foreign Aid Appropriations (FY1987), FMS Program, Genocide Convention, Greece, Grenada, Guatemala, Haiti, Hazardous Products Exports, Honduras, Human Rights (cases), Human Rights (general), India, Indonesia, Intelligence Committee.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-04 (Box 53)
  Inter-American Development Bank, Inter-American Foundation, International Atomic Energy Agency, International Bank for Reconstruction & Development, International Development Association, IDA Special Facility for Sub-Saharan Africa, International Financial Institutions (General), International Fund for Agricultural Development, IMET, IMF, International Organizations & Programs, Ireland.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-05, 1984 - 1985 (Box 115)
  Israel (3 files), Jamaica, Japan, Jordan, Korea (Republic of), Laos, Lebanon, Liberia, Libya, Mexico, Morocco, Mozambique, Namibia, New Zealand, Nicaragua (5 files), Nicaragua - Foley Amendment.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-06 (Box 119)
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 100-07, 1985, 1986, 1987, 1988, 1989 (Box 61)
  Turkey, Uganda, UN (General), UNDP, UNICEF, UNEPO, UNRMA, Vietnam, War Powers Resolution, Zaire, Zambia, Foreign Aid Appropriations FY 1988 (10 files), Foreign Aid Appropriations FY 1989 (5+ files).
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 101-01, 1989 - 1990 (Box 269)
  Afghanistan, Appropriate Technology International, African Development Foundation, AID - Africa, AID - Agriculture, AID - ASHA, AID - Central America, AID - Debt, AID - Disaster Assistance, AID - General, AID - Health, AID - Populaton, AID - PVOs, AID - Private Enterprise, AID - ROCAP, AID - Trade Development, AIPAC, Algeria, Angola, Asean, ATI, Bangladesh, Brazil, Brunei, Burkina Faso, Burma, Cambodia, Cameroon, Cape Verde, Chad, Chle, China (Mainland), China (Taiwan), Costa Rica, Covert Operations - General Legal Issues, Cuba, Cyprus, Eastern Europe, Egypt, El Salvador, El Salvador file.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 101-02, 1990 - 1991 (Box 299)
  Ethiopia, European Bank for Reconstruction & Development, Export-Import Bank, FAO Associates Experts Program, Ghana, Greece, Guatemala, Guyana, Honduras, HongKong, Human Rights Cases, Human Rights General, Hungary, International Military Education and Training, India, Indonesia, International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, International Development Association, International Financial Corporation, International Financial Institutions (general), International Fund for Agricultural Development, Inter-American Foundation, International Atomic Energy Agency, International Fund for Ireland, International Organizations and Programs, International Monetary Fund, Iraq, Ireland (2 files), Israel.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations 101-03, 1989 - 1990 (Box 300)
  Jamaica, Japan, Jewish Peace Lobby, Jordan, Kenya, Korea, Laos, Liberia, Lithuania, Madagascar, Malawi, Malaysia, Mexico, Multilateral Investment Guarantee Agency, Military Assistance, Morocco, Mozambique, Namibia, Nigeria, Nepal, Nicaragua, OPIC, Pakistan, PLO, Panama, Peace Corps, Persian Gulf (three files), Peru, Philippines, Poland, Portugal, POW/MIA, Senegal, Somalia, D of State - Narcotics, D of State - Refugees, Sudan, Syria, Turkey, Uganda, NICEF, Vietnam, Zaire, Zimbabwe.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations A, 1979 - 1980 (Box 121)
  Far East Trip Report, Floor Debate FY 1978, Foreign Military Sales, Foreign Intelligence Surveillance, Foreign Service, Foreign Operations - General, Ghana, Greece, Guatemala, Haiti, Hmong, Honduras, Hong Kong, Human Rights - General, Human Rights - Cases, Hunger Project, Inter-American Foundation, IBRD (World Bank), IBRD IDA Program Announcement, International Development Corporation Agency Proposal, International Development Association, International Development Bank FSO Loans, International Finance Corporation, India, International Military & Educational training Program, Indonesia.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations B (Box 63)
  Philippines, Philippines Base Issues, PL 480, Portugal, Public Witnesses, Recissions and Supplementals, Romania, Saudi Arabia, Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty, Secretary of State, Speech File, Sudan, South Africa, Supplementals, Somalia, Syria, Tanzania, Thailand, Trade Issues.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations c, 1982 - 1983 (Box 107)
  OMB proposed budget reduction in foreign assistance, Overseas Private Investment Corporation, Pakistan, Panama, Paraguay, Peace Corps, Peru, Pershing/Cruise Deployment, PL 480 (Food Aid to Africa), Poland, Reagan Administration (2 files), Romania, State Department (5 files), Saudi Arabia, Saudi Arabia AWACS Proposal, Security File, Secretary of State, Sinai Peacekeeping Force, Somalia, Somalia Reporgramming, South Africa, Southern Africa, Spain, Speech File, Withdrawal of US Bases in the Phillipines.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations d, 1983, 1984 (Box 44)
  McHugh notes and articles, Malaysia, Members of Congress for Peace Through Law, Mexico, Migration and Refugee Assitance, MCPL Restrictive Amendments Task Force, Middle East (General), Morocco, Most Favored Nation Status, Mozambique, Namibia, Near East, Nicaragua, Nigeria, Official Development Assistance, OPEC, Overseas Private Investment Corporation, Pakistan, Palestinians, Panama Canal, Peace Corps, Peacekeeping Activites, Peru.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Foreign Operations e, 1980 - 1984 (Box 92)
  Sudan, Surinam, Tanzania, Terrorism, Thailand, Trade Issues, Tunisia, Turkey, Uganda, UN (general), UN Development Program, UNICEF, Uruguay, Vietnam, World Food Issues (2 files), Zaire, Zimbabwe-Rhodesia.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 01 (Box 232)
  AGRICULTURE, Agriculture Land Trust, Bergland Trip to District, Cornell Briefing, Budget, COFFE (2 files), FIFRA (2 files), Ban of Use of Antibiotics in Feed, Food Stamps (4 files), Food Stamps - NYS problem, General, Cornell Human Nutrition Lab, Nesheim/Moore Meeting, National Consumer Nutrition Information Act, National Agricultural Land Policy Act.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 02, circa 1977 (Box 153)
  Legislation 1977, Nutrition (2 files), Omnibus Farm Bill (3 files), Imported Tomatoes, P L 480, Research Bill (3 files), School Lunch/Summer Feeding Programs, Timber, (Binder) Food Stamp Reform, (Binder) Food Stamp Program.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 03, 1980, 1981, 1982 (Box 54)
  Food & Drug Administration FY 1982, Food & Drug Administration: Susan Warner, Agriculture Budget FY 1981, Appropriations Overview FY 1982, Agriculture: Soil conservation 1980, Agriculture Appropriations FY 1981 Farmer’s Home Administration, Agriculture Appropriations Conference Committee FY 1982 (2 files), Food and Nutrition Service 1980, Science and Education Administration 1980 (2 files), Science and Education Administration Cornell FY 1981, Science and Education Administration FY 1981, Pine Vole Lists, Farmer’s Home Administration and Housing, RCA Review, PL 480, Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program FY 1980, Agriculture Appropriations Conference Committee FY 1980, Agricultural Marketing Service Testimony FY 1981, Secretary Bergland Testimony, Agricultural Stabilization & Conservation Service, Inspector General Testimony 1981, Farmer’s Home Administration FY 1980, Barber & Newkirk 1979, Secretary Bergland, Reconstituted Milk, Farm Credit, Farmer’s Home Administration.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 04, 1979 - 1980 (Box 93)
  Published Hearing Records, Agriculture, Rural Development, & Related Agencies Appropriations Hearings of Sub-Committee of the Committee on Appropriations of HR, 1979, parts 1-8 and 1980, parts 1-7 (bound volumes), Binghamton Dairy Hearings, February 1980 (3 files), Mark up file, Agricultural Conference FY1980 file.
- Appropriations Committee SubCommittee on Rural Development, Agriculture, and Related Agencies 05, 1979 - 1983 (Box 125)